clicktripz.com 2019-06-09

# Clicktripz - Conversion solutions for travel.

We know that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly. This notice describes our privacy policy. By visiting clicktripz.com or consenting to our tracking on a third-party website or app, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

#### What Personal Information About Customers Does Clicktripz Gather?

We may collect personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”). Personal Information is any data that may be used to identify you personally and includes email address and IP address.

The information we learn from customers helps us personalize and continually improve your shopping and web browsing experience. Here are the types of information we gather. Information You Give Us: We receive and store any Personal Information you enter on our website or give us in any other way. You can choose not to provide certain Personal Information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of certain features that rely on that information. You can opt out from having Clicktripz personalize your ads by following the instructions [here](https://www.clicktripz.com/privacy/opt_out.php). Information Shared with Us through Third Parties: Third parties may provide or provide access to personal information about you when you visit their websites. In some jurisdictions, this sharing of information requires your consent.

We use Personal Information for such purposes as responding to your requests, customizing future shopping for you, improving our marketplace, serving more relevant content and ads, and communicating with you. We aim to maintain our services in a manner that protects information from accidental or malicious destruction. Because of this, after you delete information from our services, we may not immediately delete residual copies from our active servers and may not remove information from our backup systems. Please direct any requests to access, rectify, or erase personal data via email to [privacy@clicktripz.com](mailto:privacy@clicktripz.com). Please note that in cases where we act as a data processor on behalf of a data controller, you should direct any requests to access, correct, update, or delete your personal data to the respective controller.

Non-Personally Identifiable Information: We receive and store certain types of non-personally identifiable information whenever you interact with us. For example, like many websites, we use “cookies,” (described below) and we obtain certain types of non-personally identifiable information when your web browser accesses clicktripz.com directly or through one of our partners. Such information may include the browser and type of device type being used to connect with us. A number of companies offer utilities designed to help you visit websites anonymously. Although we will not be able to provide you with a personalized experience if we cannot recognize you, we want you to be aware that these tools exist.

#### What About Cookies?

Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer’s hard drive through your web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and to provide certain features. The Help portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether.

Clicktripz collects and processes user's travel criteria, including through the use of cookies, to provide relevant offers from partnering travel websites around the web.

Third Party Cookies: We serve ads in a marketplace that may connect you to third party companies. These companies may use information (not including Personal Information such as your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to provide advertisements on clicktripz.com or one of our partners. These companies may employ their own cookies in addition to ours. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please [click here](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/).

#### Does Clicktripz.com Share the Information It Receives?

We work closely with affiliated businesses. In some cases these businesses serve ads through our marketplace. You can tell when a third party is involved by examining the content of their advertisement or webpage.

Agents: We may employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include sending and e-mail, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, providing search results and links (including paid listings and links). We share customer’s Personal Information with these agents as we deem necessary for them to perform their functions, in compliance with applicable laws.

On some travel searches we include a Google AdWord's remarketing tag in order to provide past visitors to our site with advertisements for travel deals. You may opt out of Google's use of cookies [here](https://adssettings.google.com/ "Google's Ad Settings").

Promotional Offers: We may enter into alliances, partnerships or other business arrangements with third parties for the purpose of providing you information regarding products and services that we think may be of interest to you. In addition, we may also use the Personal Information we collect to notify you about important changes to our web site, new services and special offers we think you will find valuable. If you do not want to receive such offers, please adjust your customer communication preferences on our website.

Business Transfers: As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy stores, subsidiaries, or business units. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets but remains subject to the promises made in any pre-existing Privacy Policy (unless, of course, the customer consents otherwise). Also, in the event that Clicktripz, or substantially all of its assets are acquired, customer information will of course be one of the transferred assets.

Protection of Clicktripz and Others: We release account and other Personal Information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law; enforce or apply our Terms of Use Agreement and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Clicktripz, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. Obviously, however, this does not include selling, renting, sharing, or otherwise disclosing Personal Information from customers for commercial purposes in violation of the commitments set forth in this Privacy Policy.

#### Children

Clicktripz does not sell or promote products for purchase by children. If you are under 18, you may use clicktripz.com only with the involvement of a parent or guardian.

#### Conditions of Use, Notices, and Revisions

If you choose to visit clicktripz.com or consent to tracking on a partner site, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use Agreement, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of the law of the State of California. If you have any concern about privacy at Clicktripz, please contact us with a thorough description, and we will try to resolve it. Our business changes constantly, and our Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use Agreement will change also. You should check our website to see recent changes. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Policy applies to all information that we have about you and your account.

#### Type of Data to be Processed Include:

  * Browser Name
  * Browser Version
  * Operating System
  * Device
  * Browser Language Code
  * Search History
  * IP address

##### Nature and Purpose of Processing:

Clicktripz provides a comparison shopping service, often on third party sites. Clicktripz displays targeted offers based on user search criteria, page context and other factors.

##### Duration of Processing:

The duration of the services provided by Processor to Controller.

##### Data Protection Officer:

Ryan Gibson, ryan@clicktripz.com
